I am in the sky
ashkal ʿdyd waḥb alghyna
And I love music
ana hna fy nhar walmsa'
I am a cloud in the sky
ana ghyma tndh alsma'
ana qlb fy alhwa'
atḥwl ila ḥnf
aḥb bay mwar
I am a heart in the air
I turn into a bird
aḥb bay mwar
aḥb balhwa' ila ḥnf
I hear a bird and a bird
ḥb asmʿh ṭa'r wrqya
I am a cloud in the sky
ana ghyma fy alsma' dhkya
I am a beautiful and beautiful bird
ana qd ḍmyl wshqya
I am a bird in the sky
ana qʿkat balḥl wghny
I am a cloud in the sky
wnra shwfk fyh kalkhlwf
ana ghyma tnkhafy frdw
I am a cloud in the sky
ana ghyma fy alsma'
I am a bird in the sky
aṣbḥ kafy fwa' nzl alma'
tstdwa kdha ftf fy fṣl alshyṭa'
I am a bird in the sky
ana ghyma tnkhfy frdw
ana ghyma fy alsma'
I'm in many forms and I love music
ashkal ʿdyd waḥb alghna
We are here in the river and the field
aqna hna fy alnhar walmsa'
I'm the sun that shines in the sky
ana ghyma tnkhfy frdw
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Shams shams shams, shower with shams
sms shms shms
tshryqw alsms
Shams shams shams, welcome to shams
shms shms shms
mrḥbaً ya sms
Shams shams shams, good morning to shams
shms shms
sbaḥ alkhyr ya sms
Shams shams shams, shower with shams
sms shms
tshmsw shms
Shams shams shams, you give the world a shams
shms shms
tḥdyw alarda shms
Shams shams shams, the most beautiful of shams
shms shms shms
ma ajmlk ya shms
Shams shams shams, the warm of the sun
shms shms shms
km daf'h shms
Shams shams shams, shower with shams
shms tshmswa ʿlyna
Shams shams shams, the sun is shining
daf'h ḥwlna
ṣafʿ bhbya
Shams shams shams, shower with shams
mshrq ghalyh
shms shms shms
Shams shams shams, shower with shams
tshmswa alshms
Sun, sun, sun
shms shms shms
You give the world sun
tdy' alhrd alshms
Sun, sun, sun
shms shms shms
The most beautiful sun
ma ajmlk ya shms
Sun, sun, sun
shms shms shms
You are the sun
tghrwbwa alshms
Sun, sun, sun
shms shms shms
To the meeting sun
ala allqa' ya shms
Sun, sun, sun
shms shms shms
You give the world sun
khdaً tshykh alshms
Sun, sun, sun
shms shms shms
You give the world sun
khdaً tshykh alshms
Afer, get up
aḥfr arfʿ ḥrk amly aḥfr arfʿ ḥrk amly
banish by theanim mesism
aḥfr alqlb alḥbarh aḥfr mjdarh nḥfr wana bnʿmarh
let's banish by the impet orange
hya nḥfr balḥbarh
emerging
aḥfr arfʿ ḥrk amly
söyled
Change
aḥfr arfʿ ḥrk amly
The
ḥrk bnjarh bab
clusters
ḥrk wana bnʿmarh
We are building a building
nbny brkh zbaḥh
We are moving with the 4th floor
yḥrk bnjarh bab
Move!
aḥfr arfʿ ḥrk amly
arfʿ balrafʿh
arfʿ mwajbna
nbny brjh lamʿh
nrfʿ balrafʿh
Move!
aḥfr
Left!
arfʿ
I out96 Come on move!!
ḥrk
To desseids
aḥfr
industry
byn alashar ḥywan ṣghyr
yʿysh fy alḥdyqh walḥb almsyqh
industry
asnan ṭwylh wḍnah kbyrh
aqdam ṣghyrh wdhyl ṭwyl
mn hdha alḥywan alṣghyr
The little bird is flying in a fast way
ybtwa anh yṭyr
yqfz ma yrkb shkl sryh
Oh, no, it's a little bird
yalh mn ḥywan babyh
Did you come here for a while?
hl ḥzrt mn hw؟
The little bird is flying in a fast way
asnjab asnjab
ṣghyr wnsry wnsnjab
The little bird is flying in a fast way
asnjab asnjab
bky wnbdy wnsnjab
Between the trees, a small animal
byn alashar ḥywan ṣghyr
It's flying in a fast way
ytslq bjdarh bsrʿ wmharh
It's gathering food for the winter season
yjmʿ ṭʿma lfṣl alshta'
And breaking the ordinary, that's the queen's habit
ksrat ʿady
taly mʿdt almal'h
Who is this little animal?
mn hdha alḥywan alṣghyr
It seems like it's flying
ybtwa anh yṭyr
It's moving a little bit, it's a quick shape
yqfz ma yrkb shkl sryh
Oh, no, it's a little bird
yalh mn ḥywan babyh
Did you come here for a while?
hl ḥzrt mn hw؟
The little bird is flying in a fast way
asnjab asnjab
ṣghyr wnsry wnsnjab
The little bird is flying in a fast way
asnjab asnjab
bky wnbdy wnsnjab
The little bird
asnjab
dyn swr
More than 700 pieces
akthr mn 700 fṣylh
It's big
mnha kbyrh
mnha ṣghyrh
It's long
mnha ṭwylh
And it's short
wmnha qṣyrh
More than 700 pieces
akthr mn 700 fṣylh
It's a school
mnha mftrsh
It's a bird
mnha bṭryqh
And it's short
wmnha ṣghyrh
It's a bird
dyn swr